asiancinematic.com 2012-01-20

# Privacy Policy - Asian Cinematic | Home for Japanese drama and movies, Korean, Chinese, Hong Kong and more with English subtitles download

Privacy Policy

We have created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm and continuing commitment to the privacy of personal information provided by those visiting and interacting with this web site. We hold the privacy of your personal information in the highest regard. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website.

We recognize the importance of protecting your privacy and our policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect, use and safeguard the personal information you provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our site. This policy will be continuously assessed against new technologies, business practices and our customers' needs.

**RSS Feeds and Email Updates**

If a user wishes to subscribe to my RSS Feeds or Email Updates (powered by Feedburner), I ask for contact information such as name and email address. Users may opt-out of these communications at any time. Your personal information will never be sold or given to a third party. (You will never be spammed by me - ever)

**Log Files and Stats**

This site use logs files, in this case Statcounter. This stores information such as internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring, exit and visited pages, platform used, date/time stamp, track user’s movement in the whole, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s computer tied to information about the user. This site does not use cookies. However, some of my business partners use cookies on this site (for example - advertisers). This site cannot explicitly access or control these cookies once the advertisers have set them.

**Links**

This site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we am not responsible for the privacy practices of these other sites. We suggest users to be aware of this when they leave this site and to read the privacy statements of each and every site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this site.

**Advertisers**

We use outside ad companies to display ads on this site. These ads may contain cookies and are collected by the advertising companies and we do not have access to this information. We work with the following advertising companies: (none at the moment). Please check the advertisers websites for respective privacy policies. Please note that these companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here for Google’s use of the DoubleClick DART cookie and how you may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy or go to Network Advertising Initiative to opt out of Advertising companies tracking and tailoring advertisements to your surfing patterns.

**What Information Do We Collect?**

When you visit this web site you may provide us with two types of information: personal information you knowingly choose to disclose that is collected on an individual basis and Web site use information collected on an aggregate basis as you and others browse our Web site.

**1\. Personal Information You Choose to Provide:**

_Email Information_  
If you choose to correspond with us through email, we may retain the content of your email messages together with your email address and our responses. We provide the same protections for these electronic communications that we employ in the maintenance of information received by mail and telephone.

**Sharing and Selling Information**

We do not share, sell, lend or lease any of the information that uniquely identify a subscriber (such as email addresses or personal details) with anyone except to the extent it is necessary to process transactions or provide services that you have requested.

**How Can You Access and Correct Your Information?**

You may request access to all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain in our database by emailing us at the usual address.

**What About Other Web Sites Linked to Our Web Site?**

We are not responsible for the practices employed by Web sites linked to or from our Web site or the information or content contained therein. Often links to other Web sites are provided solely as pointers to information on topics that may be useful to the users of our Web site.

Please remember that when you use a link to go from our Website to another web site, our Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. Your browsing and interaction on any other web site, including web sites, which have a link on our Website, is subject to that Web site's own rules and policies. Please read over those rules and policies before proceeding.

**Your Consent**

By using our Web site you consent to our collection and use of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. We reserve the right to amend this privacy policy at any time with or without notice.

Last Updated: 15/12/2010
